Guide to the Maritime Association of the Port of New York Records 1863-1989 MS 3093
New-York Historical Society
Maritime Association of the Port of New York records
1863-1989
New-York Historical Society
Maritime Association of the Port of New York
MS 3093
326 Linear feet in 122 boxes
{BRIEF DESCRIPTION}
Arrangement
{HOW ORGANIZED?}
Historical Note
{ABOUT MARITIME ASSOCIATION.. .}
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Maritime Association of the Port of New York, January 4, 1980, with additions in 1991.
Scope and Contents
{WHAT'S HERE?}
Maritime Association of the Port of New York/New Jersey
- Series #. Administrative and general files
  - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1877 February–1892 January
  - Minutes, Board of Directors [see note for holdings], 1873-1945
    Scope and Contents
    1873 (February) - 1886 (February)
    1885 (July) - 1890 (November)
    1894 (April) - 1897 (August)
    1901 - 1906
    1908
    1912
    1915 (April) - 1917 (July)
    1922 - 1923
    1924 (February) - 1945 (October)
  - Visitor's Register, Maritime Exchange, 1936 October 23-1970 August 3
- Series #. Membership records
  - Classified List of Members (with membership lists, by year), 1881
  - Poll List of Members, M-Z (with membership lists, by year), 1881
  - Membership Lists [see note for holdings], 1876-1942
    1876
    1877
    1883 M-Z
    1885 A - 1886 Z
    1889 A - 1904 Z
    1906 M - 1908 Z
    1921
    1928 A-Z
    1929 - 1931 A-L
    1935 - 1938 A-Z
    1939 - 1942 M-Z
  - List of officers, committee, board members (with membership lists), 1879, 1880
  - Membership Directory and Service Guide (in assorted publications), 1975
  - Special Assignment File, 1915
  - Dues, 1917
  - Certificates of Membership [see note for holdings], 1877-1955
    1879
    1882
    1883
    1885
    1887
    1888
    1896
    1902
    1905
    1907
    1913
    1917
    1935
    1945
    1950
    1955
  - Individual members (some years missing), 1877-1956
  - Individual members, A-Z, 1968-1972
  - Corporations, 1935-1950
  - Additional membership certificates and membership information files
  - Maritime Association Resignations
- Series #. Vessel casualties and breakdowns
- Series #. Vessel arrivals, departures, and berthings
- Series #. American Bureau of Shipping
  - Record of American Bureau of Shipping [see note for holdings], 1894-1976
    1894-1896
    1899-1904
    1910
    1920-1922
    1924-1976
  - Supplement to the Record of American Bureau of Shipping [see note for holdings], 1969-1976
    1969
    1974 (Supplements 1-3, 14-22)
    1976
  - Record of American Bureau of Shipping - Index of Additions and Changes [see note for holdings], 1970, 1972
    1970
    1972 (Supplements 1-20)
  - Record of American and Foreign Shipping (with Record of American Bureau of Shipping, by year) [see note for holdings], [1864]-1919
    1864 (missing)
    1871-1873
    1875
    1877-1879
    1885-1893
    1898
    1905-1914
    1916
    1918-1919
- Series #. Lloyd's papers and publications
  - Lloyd's Register of Shipping [see note for holdings], 1863-1980
    1863-1875
    1894/5-1896/7
    1898/9-1905/6
    1907/8-1913
    1915-1980
  - Lloyd's Register of Shipping Supplements [see note for holdings], 1968-1975
    1968-1972
    1973-1974
    1975 (October-December)
  - Lloyd's Register Appendix [see note for holdings], 1947-1975
    1947-1955
    1958-1975
  - Lloyd's Directory [see note for holdings], 1953-1966
    1953-1954
    1958-1966
  - Lloyd's Registry of Ships, 1866, 1868
  - Lloyd's Register of American Yachts, 1968, 1970-1972
  - Lloyd's Voyage Supplement (changes to "Lloyd's Voyage Record") [see note for holdings], 1946-1980
    1946 (December)
    1947 (January-April, June-July, September-October, December)
    1948 (January) - 1951 (December)
    1952 (January-April, July-December)
    1953 (January) - 1955 (December)
    1956 (January-June)
    1957 (January) - 1958 (September)
    1959 (January) - 1964 (December)
    1965 (April-December)
    1966 (April) - 1967 (June)
    1968 (January) - 1973 (September)
    1974
    1977-1980
  - Lloyd's Register - List of Ship Owners (with Register, by year), 1955-1968, 1989-1991
  - English Lloyd's, 1879
  - Lloyd's Casualties, 1946-1948, 1950-1981
  - Germanischer Lloyd's Register [see note for holdings], 1965-1971
    1965
    1966 (Supplements 1 and 2)
    1967 (12 Supplements)
    1968 (Supplements 1-4, 6-11)
    1970 (January-June; July 1-August 15; August 16-September 30; Vols. 5-7)
    1971 (Vols. 8-9)
- Series #. Books and other publications
  - New York Maritime Register (available on microfilm through NYPL) [see note for holdings], 1870-1941
    1870 (January) - 1875 (December)
    1876 (July) - 1884 (December)
    1885 (July) - 1893 (June)
    1894 (January) - 1900 (December)
    1901 (July) - 1904 (June)
    1905 (January) - 1914 (June)
    1915 (January) - 1939 (June)
    1941
  - New York Maritime Exchange Bulletin [see note for holdings], 1918-1971
    1918 (miscellaneous issues)
    1919 (October)
    1920 (January)
    1921 (January-September)
    1922 (June-December)
    1923 (April-December)
    1924 (July)
    1925 (February-December)
    1926 (January-November)
    1927 (January-November)
    1928 (February-June, miscellaneous issues)
    1929 (January-July)
    1930 (January-December)
    1931 (January-Decmeber)
    1932 (February-December)
    1933 (January-December)
    1934 (January-December)
    1935 (January-December)
    1936 (January-December)
    1937 (January-December)
    1938 (January-October)
    1939 (January-December)
    1940 (January-December)
    1941 (January-September, November-December)
    1942 (January-December)
    1943 (January, March-May, July, September-December)
    1944 (January, February, April, June-December)
    1945 (January, March-May, July, September, October, December)
    1946 (March, May, August, September)
    1947 (April, May, July, August, October)
    1948 (January-March, May-December)
    1949 (January-June, August-December)
    1950 (January-August)
    1951 (January-October)
    1952 (February-December)
    1953 (January-April, June, August-December; April-November miscellaneous issues)
    1954 (January, February, April, May, September-November; February-December miscellaneous issues)
    1955 (January, February, April-June, September-November; June-December miscellaneous issues)
    1956 (February-June, September, November; March-November miscellaneous issues)
    1957 (November-December; April-November miscellaneous issues)
    1958 (January-November; March, April extra issues)
    1959 (January-December)
    1960 (January, February, April-June, September-December; January-December miscellaneous issues)
    1961 (January-June, September, November December)
    1962 (January-June, September-December; January-December miscellaneous issues)
    1963 (January, March-December)
    1964 (January-December)
    1965 (Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter; January-December miscellaneous issues)
    1966 (Spring, Fall, Winter)
    1967 (Spring, Fall, Winter)
    1968 (Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter)
    1969 (Winter)
    1970 (Spring, Summer)
    1971 (Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter)
  - New York Maritime Exchange Bulletin [3 boxes miscellaneous], 1926 (May) - 1928 (April), 1964-1970
  - New York Maritime Exchange Bulletin Extracts, 1948 (December), 1949 (February), 1969 (February)
  - Naval Terms and Definitions
  - Greek Shipping Directory, 1971
- Series #. Objects
  - Brass Standards (2)
    "Members A-L"
    "Members M-Z"
  - Brass time ball
- General Files A-G, 1942-1946 (Offsite-box 1)
  Includes folders labeled
  "A" General
  Agwilines
  American Export Lines
  Anchor Line
  Annual Transportation Passes
  Association of American Railroads Correspondence
  Atlantic States Advisory Board
  Atlantic States Shipping Advisory Board
  "B" General
  Barber Lines
  Bills of Lading — Incorporation of Freight Charges
  Black Diamond SS Corp.
  Booth American Shipping Corp.
  Boyd, Weir & Sewell, Inc.
  A. H. Bull & Co.
  A. L. Burbank & Co.
  "C" General
  Caustic Soda Shipments
  Central R. R. of New Jersey
  Chilean Line
  Cosmopolitan Line
  Crude Rubber
  Cunard-White Star Line
  "D" General
  Department of Commerce Friendship Day
  Differential Rail & Water Line
  Diversion of Vessels
  Dock Strike
  D. L. & W. R. R.
  Dravo Transportainers
  Drums of Caustic Soda
  "E" General
  Embargoes
  E. C. A.
  Ellerman's Wilson Line
  Empire State Marine Co., Inc.
  Erie Railroad
  Through Export Bills of Lading
  "F" General
  Fruits & Vegetables
  New York Foreign Freight Forwarders and Brokers Association, Inc.
  Freight Forwarders
  Funch, Edye & Co.
  "Free Time on Railroads"
  "G" General
  Garcia & Diaz
  General Managers Association
  Golf Outing
  Grace Line
  Grain Delivery
  Port & Terminal Charges at U.S. Great Lakes Ports
- General Files H-R, 1938-1955 (Offsite-box 2)
  "H" General
  Heavy Lifts—Railroads
  Hearings
  Hill, Charles & Sons
  Holland America Line
  "I" General
  International Freighting Corp.
  Interstate Commerce Commission
  Isthmian SS Co.
  "J" General
  Joint Committee for the Relief of Traffic Congestion
  Joint Steamship & Railroad Committee
  "K" General
  E. J. Karr Memos
  Kerr SS Company
  "L" General
  Lehigh Valley RR
  Lighterage—Boat Demurrage
  Lloyd Brasileiro
  Luckenbach Steamship Co.
  Lumber: Suspension Charges, Unloading Docket
  "M" General
  Maritime Safety Code—Requests
  "M.S.T.S." Military Sea Transportation Service. Navy Space Charter on Cargo Vessels
  "N" General
  National Concrete Masonry Association
  New York Central RR
  New York & Cuba Mail SS Co.
  "O" General
  Ocean Rate
  Overtime on Overtime. Huron—Case
  Packaging Committee—English Bicycles
  Packaging Committee—Coconut and Cocoa Powder Pallets
  Port Loading and Unloading Charges
  Pennsylvania Railroad
  Port of New York—Pier Rentals
  Port of New York Authority
  Port Statistics
  Port Utilization, Interagency Committee
  Public Loading and Unloading at Steamship Piers
  Rowell Laboratories, Inc.
  Rules for Loading Grain
- Misc. and photos, A, B, S-W, 1944-1965 (Offsite-box 3)
  Joint Steamship & Railroad Committee, Annual Report (1944)
  Steamship Motor Carrier Bureau of NY, Inc. Memos to Executive & Policy Committees
  Rates
  United Fruit Company Hold-Backs
  Record of Longshoremen Strikes
  Proposed Economic Development Administration, New York City
  Ambrose and Scotland Lightships Marking Entrance to New York Harbor
  Brooklyn Navy Yard
  Railroad Situation (1960–61)
  Committee on alleviating truck congestion
  Convention of Tonnage Measurements of Ships
  Retirement of Samuel Wollman
  Terminal Tariffs, Docket 875
  Shippers Conference, 1947
  Vitro Corporation of America
- Misc. files, 1945-1950 (Offsite-box 4)
  Summary of Releases of Export & Coastal Freight Association of American Railroads
  Meeting of the Joint Steamship and Railroad Committee (February 29, 1952)
  Report of Activities, Joint Steamship and Railroad Committee (1950)
  Report of Activities & Minutes (1949)
  Joint Steamship & Railroad Committee Minutes (June 24, 1949)
  Joint Steamship & Railroad Committee Report of Activities (May 1949)
  J.S.S. & R.R. Committee Minutes (1948)
  J.S.S. & R.R. Committee Minutes (October 8, 1948)
  J.S.S. & R.R. Committee Minutes (1947)
  J.S.S. & R.R. Committee Minutes (1945)
  Letters to Mayor O'Dwyer and Frank Taylor re: Rentals on City-Owned Piers & Increase in Insurance Premiums
- Contracts and leases; General files 19-1 to 19-1B, 10-0A, circa 1880-1899, 1946-1956 (Offsite-box 5)
  New York State Maritime College, Section II, 19–1
  New York State Maritime College, 19–1
  New York State Maritime College (1946–1948), 19–1A
  New York State Maritime College, Exhibits, 19–1B
  Legislation (Exhibit File), 10–0A
- Files 10-1 to 10-13, 13-0-A to 13-0-149, 1949-1962 (Offsite-box 6)
  Federal Barge Lines, 10–1
  Lighterage Orders & Vessel Permits (no number)
  Overtime on Overtime, 10–2
  Diversion of Vessels, 10–3
  National Federation of American Shipping Administrative Reports (no number)
  National Federation of American Shipping, Inc., Legislative Reports, 51–93
  National Federation of American Shipping, Inc., Legislative Reports, 51–60 to 51–92
  National Federation of American Shipping, Legislative Digests, 51–30 to 51–59, 10–4–C
  National Federation of American Shipping, Legislative Digests, 82nd Cong., 1st Session, 10–4–C
  National Federation of American Shipping, Legislative Digests, 82nd Cong., 2nd Session, 10–4–C
  National Federation of American Shipping, Legislative Reports, 83rd Congress, 1st Session, 10–4–C
  Reorganization Plans, 10–5
  Coordinating Bureau on Maritime Wage Hour Suits, 10–7
  Wage Hour Suits, 10–7–A
  Lands Beneath Navigable Waters (Bills Pertaining To), 10–9
  H. R. Bills, 82nd Congress, 1st Session, 10–11–F
  H. R. Bills, 82nd Congress, 10–11–P
  Senate Bills, 82nd Congress, 1st Session, 10–12B
  Senate Bills, 81st Congress, 2nd Session, 10–12–A
  Senate Bills 10 to 81st Congress, 1st Session, 10–12
  House Joint Resolutions, 10–13
  Labor (1964–1965), 13–0–A
  Labor, Section I, 13–0–1 through 120
  Labor, Section II, 13–0–101 through 149
- Files 13-0-150 to 13-2, 1949-1958 (Offsite-box 7)
  Labor, Section III, 150 through...
  Labor, Section IV, 13–0–525 through 705
  Labor, Section V, 13–0–706 through...
  Longshormen's Strike (Oct. 15–Nov. 9), 13–0–A
  Labor (Strike), 13–0–A
  Hiring Halls, 13–1
  Hiring Halls (Exhibits), 13–1–A
  Crime Commission Hearings, Section I, 13–2
- Proceedings of Merchant Marine Council, 13-2; Minutes of joint SS and RR committee, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 8)
  Crime Commission Hearings, Section II, 13–2
  Crime Commission Exhibit File, 13–2–A
  RR Heavy Lift Charges
- Misc. files and 1952 SS lighter report; Weekly information bulletin, 1952-1970 (Offsite-box 9)
- Tariff Board regulations; File 18-0, 1949-1964 (Offsite-box 10)
- Lighter and railroad reports, 1954-1961 (Offsite-box 11)
  Record of Steamers Receiving Lighters, Saturday & Sunday
  Reports sent to: Association of American Railroads—Lighters detained over 48 hours—for embargo purposes
  Baltimore & Ohio Railroad
  Jersey Central Line
  Erie-Lackawanna Railroad
- Aircraft types, railroad reports; Files 17-2 to 17-11, 1941-1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  Aircraft Types & Prices
  Lehigh Valley Railroad
  New York Central Railroad
  Guy De Berc Private Testimonial Dinner (April 28, 1966)
  National Maritime Day, 17–2
  National Marine Exposition, 17–4
  Citation to Benjamin Parry (December 15, 1948), 17–5
  Luncheon Tendered to Messrs. Blanchard, Helleher, Moran & Karr, 17–7
  Luncheon Tendered to James A. Farrell & Myron Bull, 17–8
  Luncheon Tendered to Rear Admiral Monroe Kelly, 17–9
  Luncheon for Messrs. Barber & Bull, 17–10
  Golden Anniversary of the City of New York, 17–11
- Files 17-11A to 17-20A, 1943-1963 (Offsite-box 13)
  Golden Anniversary of the City of New York, Exhibits, 17–11–A
  Luncheon Tendered to Messrs. Kelleher & Barber, 17–12
  Testimonial Meeting, Randall & Karr, 17–13
  Luncheon Tendered to Commodore F. G. Reinicke, 17–14
  Luncheon Tendered to Admiral Joseph F. Farley, 17–15
  Salvage of Ships by Geo. R. Critchley, 17–16
  Ceremony in Honor of Crew of U.S. Coast Guard Cutter "Bibb" (Rescue), 17–17
  Luncheon tendered to Honorable Charles Sawyer, 17–18
  Special Luncheon Honoring Commodore F. G. Reinicke, 17–19
  Port of New York Day Celebration, 17–20 (multiple folders)
- Files 17-20C to 17-33, 1947-1962 (Offsite-box 14)
  Port of New York Day Ceremonies, 17–20
  Police Athletic League, 17–21
  Lifeboat Race, 17–22
  Luncheon for Messrs: Farrell Jr. and John F. Gehan, 17–23
  Luncheon Hon. Robert W. Dill, 17–24
  New York City's 300th Anniversary, Inc. (1953), 17–25
  Testimonial Luncheon Honoring Admiral E. J. Moran, 17–26
  Maritime Industry Special Events, 17–27
  Children's Christmas Fund (1947), (no number)
  Employees' Christmas Fund (1947), (no number)
  Employees' Christmas Fund, 17–28
  Testimonial Luncheon Honoring Newbold T. Lawrence, Lewis A. Lapham, 17–29
  Testimonial Luncheon Honoring Lewis A. Lapham, Edward J. Barber, 17–30
  Hudson River Celebration, 17–31
  Ted Gilsenan Testimonial Dinner, 17–32
  Port of New York Day, 17–33
- Ship sales, 1958-1982 (Offsite-box 15)
- US Army Engineers, Coast Guard, and Mariners, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 16)
- Lighter reports, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 17)
- Lighter reports, maps, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 18)
- NYU Bellevue Fund; PT reports, 1944-1948 (Offsite-box 19)
- General Files A-Ch, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 20)
  American Legion—Robert L. Hague Post No. 1242
  American West African Line—From N.Y. to Charleston and Savannah
  Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association
  Baltimore Port Bulletin
  E. J. Barber (President)
  Barge Canal (New York State) Legislation
  Extension Battery Park Wall
  Captain Blanchard
  Hon S. O. Bland
  Board of Investigation & Research
  Captain C. S. Bookwalter, De-O, USNR (Ret.)
  Boston Maritime Exchange
  British American Ambulance Corps (Posters)
  Brooklyn Battery Bridge [crossed out] Tunnel
  Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce
  Bulletin—Subversive Activities
  Bureau of Internal Revenue
  Bureau of Marine Inspection & Navigation
  Canal File
  Captain of Port Orders
  Chamber of Commerce of U.S.A. Foreign Commerce Dept. Committee
  Claim Agents Committee
- General Files Cl-F, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 21)
  Captain Everett D. Capehart, U.S.N (Ret.)
  Chamber of Commerce
  Claims Committee
  Captain Granville Conway
  Coast Guard Anchorages. Map & Launch Landings
  Coast Guard Blackout Suggestions
  Coast Guard Identification Cards
  Coast Guard & Navy Conference on Ship Security
  Coast Guard. Merchant Marine Council, Washington
  Commerce and Industry Association
  Coastwise Laws (Waiver)
  Custom House Regulations
  Department of Commerce
  Department of Marine and Aviation (Dock Department)
  Department of State. Agreement between U.S. and Iran
  Directory: Membership, Maritime Association, N.Y.
  Dock Commissioner
  Edwin H. Duff
  Joseph B. Eastman
  Explosives
  Federal Bureau of Investigation
  Ferry File
  Ferry Services to Brooklyn
  Fire Ordinance, No Smoking Law
  Fire Prevention Orders (Sub-Committee, W. F. Firth, Chairman)
  Fire Prevention Regulations
  Commander J. J. Flynn, U.S.C.G.
  Foreign Commerce Club of New York
  Foreign Policy Association, Inc.
  Foreign Trade Policy
  Foreign Trade Zone
  Fumigation File
  Freeports
- General Files G-M, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 22)
  Golf Committee
  Golf Tournament
  Gregory A. Harrison
  I. and S. Docket 5110. The Deming Rate Bases
  I.C.C. Canned Goods
  Insurance Cos. Financial Statements
  Inter-American Foreign Trade and Arbitration
  Intercoastal Service
  International Longshoremen Association
  Joint Steamship and Railroad Committee
  Journal of Commerce Shipping Article
  E. J. Karr
  J. J. Kelleher
  Kilgore Report
  Labor File
  Lake Carriers Association
  Roger D. Lapham, Mayor of San Francisco
  Lighterage
  Lighters—Hold Backs (Kohl)
  Lighter Captains' Union
  Lloyd's of London Temporary File
  Luncheon—Secretary Knox
  Luckenbach Company
  "Mc"
  Marine News Department
  Marine Borers
  Marine Index Bureau
  Maritime Commission
  Marshalls Covering Sales Vessel Property
  Mayor's Committee on Ports & Terminals, File #3 (Mayor La Guardia)
  Eugene F. Moran
- General Files N-O, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 23)
  National Association of Stevedores
  National Foreign Trade Council, Inc.
  National Rivers & Harbors Congress
  National Safety Council
  National Trucking Association
  Neutrality Bill
  N. J. Lighterage Case, 1941
  New Orleans. Miscellaneous Data. C.H.C. Took on Trip
  New York State Maritime Academy
  New York State Merchant Marine Academy
  New York State Waterway Association
  N.Y. at War Parade (June 13, 1942)
  New York State Waterways Association
  Newark Bay Survey
  Nominating Committee
  Obituaries
  Office of Defense Administration
  Office of Defense Transportation
  Office of Price Administration, New Orleans Steamship Association
  Oil
  One Day Institute on Middle America and the United States
- General Files P-R, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 24)
  "P" General
  Panama Canal
  Pay-As-You-Go Income Tax Plan
  Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. (Accountants)
  Piers (North River & N.Y. Free Port Zone)
  Pooling Railroad Facilities
  Charlie Potter
  Priorities
  Produce Exchange Time Charter
  Propeller Club
  Purchasing Agents
  "Q" General
  "R" General
  Association of American Railroads
  Railroad Embargo
  Railroad Land Grants
  Railroad Membership
  Railroad Strike; Rationing Regulations for Gasoline
  Rationing Regulations for Tires, Etc.
  Red Cross War Fund
  Renegotiation Act
  Research Institute of America
  Resolutions
  Rivers, Harbors & Piers, N.Y. & N.J. Channels, Buttermilk Channel
  Rivers, Harbors & Piers Committee
  Nelson A. Rockefeller article, "Will We Remain Good Neighbors After the War?," Saturday Evening Post, November 6, 1943
  Rope for the Loading and Discharging of Ships
  Ruml Tax Plan
- General Files S, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 25)
  "S" General
  Safety Code—Maritime—Stevedoring—Longshormen
  San Francisco Marine Exchange
  Schedule of Rates for Lighters and Stevedores
  Seaway for Defense Committee
  Albert Serkes
  Shipbuilders—Membership Campaign
  Ship Chandlers
  Ship Operators Association, Inc.
  Shippers Conference of Greater New York
  Shipping Priorities
  Shipping Situation—Admiral Land as Administrator, Coastwise Shipping
  Smoke Fine
  Social Security in Private Enterprise
  Staffing Schedule for Saltwater Freighters & Tankers of 7,000 to 11,000 gr. Tons
  State Department Releases
  St. Lawrence
  Stevedore File
  Stevedoreing Committee
  Unemployment Insurance for Seamen
- General Files L-Z, 1944 (Offsite-box 26)
  Leather
  Lighters
  Obituary
  Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co.
  Pocket Liberty Vessel
  Pooling of Shipping
  Port Conditions Committee
  Port Coordinator's Security Group
  Port of New York—Maritime Exchange Committee for Safety and Welfare
  Port Security Groups; Port Stewards Association
  Port Terminals
  Postwar
  Railroad Information; Rivers, Harbor and Piers
  Safety and Security—Maritime Exchange Committee for the Safety and Security of the Port of New York
  Seamen's Church Institute of New York—Modernization Fund
  Seatrain Lines
  Ship Design
  Smoking Violations
  Social Security Laws
  Social Security Tax
  Staffing Schedule for Salt Water Freighters and Tankers
  Charles I. Stanfield
  Steamship Historical Society of America
  Terminal Stevedoring Co.
  Traffic Bulletin
  Truck Terminal
  Tunnel
  United Fruit Company
  United Maritime Authority Planning Committee
  Victory Fleet Day (September 27, 1944)
  Western Union Telegraph; Wharfage
  James B. Young (Barber Steamship Lines, Inc.)
- General Files I-P, 1945 (Offsite-box 27)
  Includes folders (some with crumbled, illegible tabs) labeled
  ICC Class Rate Decision
  Ice Conditions
  Interstate Commerce Act
  Junk Boats
  E. J. Karr—Testimonials
  Kelleher, J. J. (Director)
  Labor Management Conference
  La Guardia, Mayor F. H.
  Legislation, Air
  Lewis, Jr., Arthur, c/o Seas Shipping Co., Inc.
  Lightships (Barnegat, Scotland, and Fire Island)
  Marine Aviation Department
  Marine News
  Marine Terminal Operating Committee
  Maritime Building Re: Painting, etc.
  Maritime Association of the Port of New York
  M. A. Mendlesen, Personal
  Eugene F. Moran, Sr.
  Murphy, E. J., Personal
  Navy Day (October 27, 1945)
  New York Board of Trade
  New York State Maritime Academy, Ft. Schuyler, N.Y.
  New York State Waterways
  New York Tow Boat Exchange
  Newspapers, etc.—Publications
  New Jersey Ship Canal
  North Atlantic Ports Conference
  Panama Canal / Panama Railroad Co.
  Panama Canal Zone
  Parker, Rear Adm. S. V., Reception
  Photographs